H. Alexander Smith Papers, 1897-1966 (bulk 1920-1966 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 3: New Jersey Politics, 1919-1945; 50.46 linear feet 121 boxes
  - Subseries 3D: Public Relations, 1934-1944; 1.25 linear feet 3 boxes
    The Public Relations Subseries includes material detailing Smith's relations with the media, vis-à-vis the New Jersey Republican Party, through newspaper clippings, press releases and press statements. The bulk of the subseries consists of newspaper clippings, whose content relates to either Smith or the New Jersey Republican Party and their activities. The press releases and press statements are all from the New Jersey Republican Party.
    The Public Relations Subseries is divided into three groups: Newspaper Clippings, Press Releases and Press Statements, arranged alphabetically by group. The newspaper clippings are arranged alphabetically by subject. The press releases and press statements are arranged chronologically.
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1934-1944; 3 boxes (1 partial)
      - Alcoholic Beverage Control Committee, Appointment, 1941; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Campaigns, 1942-1944; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Edison, Governor, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Hawkes, A. W, 1942; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Highway, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - National, 1934-1936; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - National Defense, 1940-1942; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey Counties, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Oxford Group, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Political, 1942; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Post-Election, 1941; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Rail Road Tax Bill, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Smith, H. A, 1941; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - State Government, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937-1942; portions of 2 boxes
        - 1937-1939, 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - 1941, 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - 1942, 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1941 June-1944; 6 folders
      - 1941 June-August, 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - 1941 September, 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - 1941 October, 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - 1941 November, 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - 1941 December, 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - 1944, 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Press Statements, 1939-1940; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Series 4: Senatorial Career, 1931-1958; 159.67 linear feet 376 boxes
  The Senatorial Career Series documents Smith’s tenure as a Untied States Senator from New Jersey and is the largest series in the collection by far. This series reflects Smith’s devotion to the Senate Foreign Relations Committee and his general interest in Communism and Far East Asia. Domestic issues of interest to Smith included labor and management relations and projects related to his home state of New Jersey. Documents include campaign literature, correspondence, press releases, newspaper clippings, legislation, reports, and memoranda. Some photographs are also included.
  The Senatorial Career Series is divided into seven subseries: Campaigns, Correspondence, Media and Public Relations, Proposed Bills and Voting Record, Public Issues, Senate Committees, and Speeches and Addresses. The subseries are arranged alphabetically.
  - Subseries 4A: Campaigns, 1943-1958; 6.67 linear feet 16 boxes
    The Campaigns Subseries documents Smith’s senate campaigns, most notably the campaigns of 1944, 1946 and 1952. Also included are documents related to various Republican campaigns in New Jersey. Correspondence constitutes the bulk of the documents. Notable correspondence includes letters between Smith and local and national party leaders discussing strategy and platforms. Also included are numerous letters of congratulations. Other documents include election returns, data, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, and posters.
    The Campaigns Subseries is arranged chronologically by election year.
    - Smith, 1944 Senate Campaign, 4 boxes (1 partial)
      - Advertising, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Candidacy, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Committee Meeting, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Congratulations, Letters of, 1944; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - Election, A-C, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Election, D-G, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Election, H-L, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Election, M-P, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Election, R-S, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Election, T-Z, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Election, Miscellaneous, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Induction, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Nomination, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Convention, State, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Farm Policy, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Induction Ceremony, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Negro Data, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Newark Headquarters, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Polish Groups, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Primary Returns, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Princeton Committee, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Smith Family, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Speech Material, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Tax Legislature, 1943; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Ukrainian Groups, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Veterans, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Veterans Data, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Voting Machine Data, 1943; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Vouchers, Election Campaign Fund, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Ware, Elmer H, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - White, Weld and Company, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Wittreich, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Women’s Activities, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Women’s Republican Clubs, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Young Republicans, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Youth and Government, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Smith, 1946 Senate Campaign, 3 boxes (2 partial)
      - A, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - B, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Buell, Raymond L, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - C, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - County, Bergen, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - County, Hudson, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - County, Passaic and Union, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - D, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Driscoll Nomination, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - E, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Election Data, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - F, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - G, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - H-L, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - M-N, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - New Jersey Republican Finance Committee, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - New Jersey Republican State Committee, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - P, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Primary, Bank Account, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - R, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Republican National Committee, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - S, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Senatorial Campaign, 1946; portions of 2 boxes
        - Advertising, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Armenian, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Congratulations, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Jewish, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Labor, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Matter, Jones, Mark, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Newspapers, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Press Releases, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Printing, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Publicity, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Reprints, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Voting Record, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - T-Z, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Smith, 1952 Senate Campaign, 7 boxes (2 partial)
      - Alexander, Archibald, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Appreciation Letters, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Doctors, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Farm Group, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Finances, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Lists, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Nurses, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Pamphlets, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Pharmacists, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Political Notebook, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Stevenson, Adlai, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Ukrainian, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952; 2 folders (Folder 1 to 2)
      - Congratulations, Letters of, to Elected, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Congratulations, Letters of, to Smith, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Congratulations, Letters of, to Smith, 1952; 2 folders (Folder 1 to 2)
      - Memos, Speeches, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Campaign Issues, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - New Jersey Republican State Committee, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Speakers, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Campaign Correspondence, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Twitchell, H. K, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Forgotten Mailman, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Civil Service, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Slovak, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Jewish Letter, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Doctors, Dentists and Nurses, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Gray Letter, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Italian, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - "Here’s What a Republican Congress Did For You,", 1952; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Ministries, Bowlby, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Retailers, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Poultry, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Teachers, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Liberation Rally, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Record of Campaign Literature, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Lists, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Voting Record, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Veterans Administration, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Reprints, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Cain Material, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Farm, Aiken, Grain, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - New Jersey Ethnic Groups, Statistics and Data, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - A, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Alexander, Archibald, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - B, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Barry, Thomas, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - C, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Civil Rights, Correspondence, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Civil Rights, Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Challengers, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Convention Headquarters, Newark, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - D, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Driscoll, Alfred, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Dirksen-Smith, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - E, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Employment, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Endorsements, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - F, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Farm Journal, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Forbes, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Gabrielson, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - H, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Hermann, Albert B, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - I, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - L, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Lewis, Sam, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - M, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - N, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - P, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Postal, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Press Conference, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Petitions, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - R, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Radio, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Ring, Carl, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - S, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Smith for President, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Stevenson, Frank, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - T, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Taft Campaign, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - V, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - W, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Reelection, Newspapers, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Campaign Releases, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Congress of Industrial Organizations, Publications, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Negro Activities for Reelection of United States Senator H. Alexander Smith, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Republican Campaigns, 1944-1958; 3 boxes (2 partial)
      - County Reports, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Hannold Report, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - New Jersey, Republican, General, 1951-1955; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - New Jersey State Platforms, 1946-1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - New Jersey State Republican Convention, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - New Jersey State Republican Platform, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Republican Conference, Chairmanship, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Republican Conference, Miscellaneous, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Republican National Convention, New Jersey Delegates, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Republican National Convention, Platform, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Republican National Convention, Miscellaneous, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Republican National Platforms, 1944-1956; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Republican Policy, Russell Davenport, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Republican Policy Committee, 1951-1955; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Resolutions Committee, Convention, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Studer Report, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1943-1952; 3 boxes (1 partial)
      - Articles and Interviews, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Comments on Smith’s Releases and Speeches, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Congressional Elections, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Driscoll Campaign, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Election Results, General Election, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Foreign Policy, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Labor, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Palestine Issue, Jewish Voters, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Pamphlets, 1948-1951; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Press Releases, Deadlines, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Press Releases, Princeton, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Press Releases, Reprints, 1946-1948; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Republican Campaign, Dewey, Warren, Hendrickson, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Republican National Convention, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Republican Senatorial Committee, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Speeches, 1944-1945; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Taxes, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Unemployment Compensation, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Washington, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 item
  - Subseries 4B: Correspondence, 1943-1958; 18.35 linear feet 44 boxes
    The Correspondence Subseries contains Smith's personal and business correspondence. The bulk of the material is not directly related to Smith’s work in the Senate but covers the same timeframe. Some of the material does relate to issues and causes that Smith was involved in through the Senate. The subjects of most of the correspondence include letters related to Princeton, letters to and from family members, cards, and documents related to personal finance.
    The Correspondence Subseries maintains Smith's original arrangement into sections organized chronological by year. Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject or correspondent within each section.
    - 1943-1948, 3 boxes (1 partial)
      - Personal Letters, Smith to Wife, 1943-1948; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Belgian-American Education Foundation, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Belgian-American Educational Foundation and Similar Organizations, 1943-1948; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Christmas Greetings, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Clark, H. B, 1943-1948; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Congratulations, Senate Session, 80th Congress 1st, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Dominick and Dominick, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Dominick and Dominick, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Dominick and Dominick, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Dominick and Dominick, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Dominick, Gayer G, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Election Data, 1944-1946; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Foreign Policy Association, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Foreign Policy Association, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Foreign Policy Association, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Lease, 81 Alexander St., Princeton, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Princeton, Class of, 1901; 1946; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Princeton, Class of, 1901; 1947; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Princeton University, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Princeton, Class of, 1901; 1945; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Princeton University, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Princeton, Class of, 1901; 1948; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Murray Bay Vacation, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Crane, Jasper E, 1943-1948; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Dominick, Gayer G, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Princeton Bicentennial, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Princeton University Bicentennial, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - European Trip, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Princeton University Data, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Salaries, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Salaries, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Salary, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Salary, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Oath of Office, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Twitchell, H. Kenaston, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Voting Record, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Smith, Mrs. H. Alexander, 1943-1948; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Personal, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - 1945-1949, 6 boxes (2 partial)
      - Personal, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Birthday, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Retirement Fund, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Smith, Helen Dominick, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Smith, H. Alexander, Jr, 1945-1949; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Personal, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Ladies of the Senate, Mrs. Smith, 1947-1949; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Shoemaker, Mrs. Samuel M., Jr, 1945-1949; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Twitchell, H. K, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Twitchell, H. K, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - A, 1946-1949; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Belgium American Educational Foundation, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Mrs. Howard Bruce, 1945-1949; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Christmas, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Crane, Jasper E, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Dominick and Dominick, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Foreign Policy Association, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - L, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Mastigouche Club, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Princeton University Data, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Q, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - S, 1947-1949; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Salary, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Smith, Jr., H. Alexander, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Personal, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Paid Bills, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Smith, Helen Dominick, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Truman, President Harry S, 1945-1949; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Vacation, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Vacation, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Washington Apartment, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - White, Weld and Company, 1945-1949; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Memoranda, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Birthday, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Office Correspondence, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - A, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Alaska Statehood, 1945-1949; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Beach Erosion, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - C, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Corwin, George B., Youth Government YMCA, Boy Governors Conference, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Clark, William, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - D, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Driscoll, Alfred E., Governor, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Driscoll Campaign, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - E, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - F, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - G-K, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Librarians in New Jersey, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - L, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - M, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - New Jersey Republican Finance Committee, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey State Chamber of Commerce, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - New Jersey State Committee, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - N, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - O, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Princeton Hospital, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Q, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Rutgers University, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - R, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - S, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Personal, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - T, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - V, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Van Nest, John, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Watson Laboratories, Rome, New Jersey, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - W, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - X-Z, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - 1949-1953, 8 boxes (2 partial)
      - Foreign Policy Association, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Congressional Club, 1949-1953; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Hoover’s Birthday, 1949-1953; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - R, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - P, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Hoover, Herbert, 1949-1953; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Princeton, Class of, 1901; 1949; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - "Get Well" Letters, Cards, 1950 April; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Personal, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Twitchell, H. K, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - European Trip, 1950 September; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Vacation, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - B, 1952-1953; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - C, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - D, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Dominick, Mr. Gayer G., 1950-53, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Foreign Policy Report, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Foreign Policy Association, Personal, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - United States Senate Memorandum, 1949-1953; 2 folders (Folder 7 to 8)
      - A, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - B, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - C, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Christmas, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - D, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Dominick and Dominick, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - E, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - F, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - G, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Ha, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Ho, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Irwin, Wallace, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - J, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Ke, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Kn, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Fulton Lewis Questionnaire, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Ma, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Mc, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Mo, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Mi, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - P, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Princeton Reunion of Class of, 1901; 1950; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Robie, Edward, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - S, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Shoemaker, Mr. and Mrs, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Twitchell, H. K, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Personal, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Birthday, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Birthday, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Smith, Schuyler, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - T, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - U-V, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - W, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Washington Apartment, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - A-C, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - D-G, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 1)